瞧,Gary!
Look, Gary!
那个警察正朝你挥手呢.
That policeman's waving to you.
他想要你停下来.
He wants you to stop.
你认为你现在是在哪儿?
Where do you think you are?
在赛车道上吗?
On a race track?
你刚才一定是以每小时70英里的速度开车.
You must have been driving at seventy miles an hour.
我不可能开得那么快的.
I can't have been.
我是以每小时80英里的速度超过你的.
I was doing eighty when I overtook you.
难道你没看见限速牌吗?
Didn't you see the speed limit?
我恐怕我没有看见,警官.
I'm afraid I didn't, officer.
我一定思想开小差了.
I must have been dreaming.
警官,他思想没有开小差.
He wasn't dreaming, officer.
我刚才正告诉他开慢点.
I was telling him to drive slowly.
所以我才没看见那牌子.
That's why I didn't see the sign.
让我看一看你的驾驶执照.
Let me see your driving licence.
这次我就不罚你款了.
I won't charge you this time.
但你最好不要再犯.
But you'd better not do it again!
谢谢您.我以后一定会多加注意.
Thank you. I'll certainly be more careful.
Gary,我刚才叫你开慢点吧.
I told you to drive slowly, Gary.
你总是叫我开慢点,亲爱的.
You always tell me to drive slowly, darling.
Well,下次你最听从我的劝告!
Well, next time you'd better take my advice!